Guide to the Gay men's popular fiction collection, 1931-1992
Gay men's popular fiction collection, 1931-1992
- Randolph, Peter, God Save The Queen!, Greenleaf Classics, GL 121, 1969 (Box 25)
- Randolph, Peter, Sextet, Guild Press Ltd., -0-, 1967 (Box 27)
- Randolph, Peter, Beat It, Kid!, Guild Press Ltd., TC104, 1968 (Box 28)
- Rank, David, Queer For Muscle, Surey Books, HIS 69564, 1987 (Box 80)
- Rank, David, Eight The Hard Way, Surey Books, HIS 69576, n.d. (Box 80)
- Raul, K. B., Naked To The Night, Paperback Library, 53-285, 1964 (Box 41)
- Raul, K. B., A Hidden Hunger, Paperback Library, 55-724, 1968 (Box 41)
- Rawlings, Russell, Golden Shower Boys, Greenleaf Classics, AC170, 1977 (Box 91)
- Ray, Lowell, Brown Eye Boy, Surrey House, MH 453, 1974 (Box 82)
- Reage, Pauline, The Wisdom Of The Lash, Olympia Press, no. 44, n.d. (Box 38)
- Rechy, John, City Of Night, Grove Press, 1296, 1963 (Box 19)
- Rechy, John, Numbers, Grove Press, B 171, 1967 (Box 19)
- Rechy, John, This Day's Death, Grove Press, B-301-Z, 1969 (Box 19)
- Redman, Rod, Gay Semester, Private Editions Books, PE 500, 1969 (Box 49)
- Reed, Lance, Rough Boys In Denim, Star Dist., SS-1006, 1976 (Box 66)
- Reese, Stan, The Lucky Pick Up, Star Dist., Club 103, 1973 (Box 59)
- Reich, Kyle, Macho Brother, Arena, GB 115, 1978 (Box 2)
- Reich, Kyle, Night Of The Animals, Arena, GB 118, 1978 (Box 2)
- Reich, Kyle, Teacher In Chains, Arena, GB 128, 1979 (Box 2)
- Reinhart, Robert, A History Of Shadows, Avon, 0-380-79616-3-295, 1982 (Box 4)
- Renzi, John, Gay Awakening, Parisian Press, P 211, 1972 (Box 41)
- Reskind, Jon, The Stepson, Tiburon Publishing Co., LLP 206, 1970 (Box 87)
- Revel, Mark, Anatomy Of A Super Stud, Classic Pubns., CP 548, 1969 (Box 13)
- Ricco, Mario, Little Boy Gay, 101 Enterprises, 101-12, 1968 (Box 40)
- Rice, Walter, Balcony Bunnies *, 101 Enterprises, 101-20, 1967 (Box 40)
- Rich, Gary, Sailors And Their Boys, 101 Enterprises, 101-3, 1967 (Box 39)
- Richards, Chuck, Muscle Master, Star Dist., SS-1017, 1978 (Box 66)
- Richards, Mark, Stud For Sale, Arena, DS 111, 1982 (Box 1)
- Richards, Mark, G.I. Jock, Arena, DS 115, 1982 (Box 1)
- Richards, Mark, Hard At Play, Arena, DS 121, 1983 (Box 1)
- Richards, Mark, Jock On The Road, Arena, DS 125, 1983 (Box 2)
- Richards, Mark, Special Delivery, Arena, DS 144, 1984 (Box 2)
- Richards, Paul, Big Daddy's Boy, 101 Enterprises, 101-7, 1968 (Box 39)
- Richardson, Humphrey, The Sexual Life Of Robinson Crusoe, Olympia Press, TC-205, 1962 (Box 39)
- Richler, Mordecai, Cocksure, Bantam Books, 553-04390, 1968 (Box 6)
- Richter, Art, Butt Busting Buddies, Surrey House, HIS 69122, 1974 (Box 72)
- Richter, Art, Turning The Screw, Surrey House, HIS 69130, 1975 (Box 72)
- Richter, Art, Sucker For Seafood, Surrey House, MH 471, 1974 (Box 82)
- Richter, John, Bangin' Buddies, Surree Ltd, HIS 69146, 1975 (Box 73)
- Ricksen, Owen, Carney Boy Vol 1, Monkey Pubn., -0-, 1969 (Box 36)
- Ricksen, Owen, Rub the Man Down, Monkey Publication, -0-, 1969 (Box 91)
- Rico, Don, The Man From Pansy, Lancer, 73-578, 1967 (Box 34)
- Rico, Don, The Daisy Dilemma, Lancer, 73-639, 1967 (Box 34)
- Riddle, Jack *, Hard-Loving Brothers, Rough Trade, RT 435, n.d. (Box 55)
- Rider, Jack, The Denim Boys, Star Dist., HS 1010, 1975 (Box 62)
- Rig, Lance, Texas Gang Rape, Rough Trade, RT 450, n.d. (Box 55)
- Rig, Lance, Broken Boy, Star Dist., SS-1009, 1976 (Box 66)
- Riggins, Mitchell, Firehouse Rookie, Star Dist., SS-1014, 1977 (Box 66)
- Riggles, Jon, Country Cousin, Encounter Books, EE 106, 1978 (Box 16)
- Riggles, Jon, Chauffeur For Hire, Janus Studios, DN-120, 1978 (Box 33)
- Riggles, Jon, Like Father, Like Son, Maverick, EE 101, 1978 (Box 15)
- Riggles, Jon, Hollywood Hot, Maverick, EE 103, 1978 (Box 15)
- Riggles, Jon, His Cycle Master, Surree Ltd, HIS 69233, 1978 (Box 76)
- Riggles, Jon, Leather Sucker, Surree Ltd, HIS 69411, 1980 (Box 79)
- Riggles, Jon, Big Bad Boss, Surree Ltd, SSS 107, 1981 (Box 86)
- Riggles, Jon, Trapped & Tied!, Surree Ltd, SSS 112, 1981 (Box 86)
- Riley, Brad, The Intruders, Private Editions Books, PE 382, 1966 (Box 48)
- Riley, Rick, Savage Stud, Star Dist., SS-1033, 1979 (Box 67)
- Rinker, David L., My Teacher, My Lover, Parisian Press, P 203, 1971 (Box 41)
- Rinker, David L., City Boys, Parisian Press, P 226, 1972 (Box 42)
- Rippe, Peter, Ream Rodded Lover, Star Dist., WB 104, 1975 (Box 67)
- Robbins, T. H., Summer Stock Superstud, GX, Inc., TC 262, 1973 (Box 31)
- Roberto, Satyricon 70, Midwood, M-175-21, 1970 (Box 35)
- Roberts, Brad, The Greek Touch, P. E. C., FL 51, 1968 (Box 51)
- Roberts, Brad, The Greek Touch, P. E. C., FL 58, 1969 (Box 52)
- Roberts, Lance, Geisha Boy, GX, Inc., TC 209, n.d. (Box 29)
- Roberts, Lance, A Hand In The Bush, GX, Inc., TC 242, n.d. (Box 31)
- Roberts, Mack, Making Scott Fry, GX, Inc., SB 602, 1973 (Box 28)
- Roberts, Nick, Get Thee Behind Me, Phenix Publishers, PR 243, 1969 (Box 45)
- Roberts, Pudgey, Dormitory Mates, 101 Enterprises, 101-14, 1968 (Box 40)
- Roberts, Pudgey, Seafood, 101 Enterprises, 101-41, 1969 (Box 92)
- Roberts, Thomas, Chicken Lickin' Good, Surrey House, MH 466, 1974 (Box 82)
- Roberts, Todd, Behind The Man, Surree Ltd, HIS 69410, 1980 (Box 79)
- Robertson, Pete, Jocks In Bondage, Arena, MP 133, 1984 (Box 3)
- Robinson, C.J. Bradbury, Bare Knees, Boy Knees, Greenleaf Classics, PR 299, 1971 (Box 46)
- Robinson, C. J. Bradbury, A Crocodile Of Choirboys, Phenix Publishers, PR 283, 1970 (Box 46)
- Robles, Chuck, Mountain Men, Arena, PF-129, 1984 (Box 3)
- Robyn, Jason, The Young And Gay, Valley Circle Pubn., SV 107, 1972 (Box 88)
- Roger, Love, Global Press, FGL 18, 1970 (Box 38)
- Rogers, Alexis, Cost of Love, Lavender Press, -0-, 1990 (Box 94)
- Rogers, Bart, Trucker Bone, Star Dist., HS 508, 1977 (Box 62)
- Rogers, Boyd, Sucking Seamen, Rough Trade, RT 406, n.d. (Box 54)
- Rogers, Dan, Troubled Lovers, F.S. Publishing, GPL 103, n.d. (Box 17)
- Rogers, Harvey, Everyone's Ball Boy, Star Dist., CC-104, 1977 (Box 59)
- Rogers, L.K., Dock Strip, Rough Trade, RT-458, n.d. (Box 92)
- Rogers, Lance, Getting It All Together, F.S. Publishing, GW 108, n.d. (Box 18)
- Rogers, Lance, Cream Of The Crop, GX, Inc., GH 2001, n.d. (Box 28)
- Rogers, Lance, Searchlight Insight, GX, Inc., TC 203, n.d. (Box 29)
- Rogers, Lance, Leave The Driving To Us, GX, Inc., TC 205, n.d. (Box 29)
- Rogers, Lance, A Fistful Of Miracles, GX, Inc., TC 235, n.d. (Box 30)
- Rogers, Lance, Mutual Palmistry, GX, Inc., TC 238, n.d. (Box 30)
- Rogers, Lance, Lord Of The Flys, GX, Inc., TC 244, 1972 (Box 31)
- Rogers, Lance, Pulling A Boner, GX, Inc., TC 250, 1973 (Box 31)
- Rogers, Lance, Comin' Thru The Y, XXX Inc., GW 125, n.d. (Box 18)
- Rogers, Marshall, The Unwilling Rape, Greenleaf Classics, PR 394, 1973 (Box 48)
- Rogers, Mick, Freakout On Sunset Strip, Greenleaf Classics, GC 221, 1967 (Box 24)
- Rogers, Tom, Easy To Be Hard, Surrey House, MH 412, 1973 (Box 81)
- Rogers, Tom, Come Free, Surrey House, MH 435, 1974 (Box 82)
- Roman, Chet, Gay Guy, Greenleaf Classics, GL 144, 1969 (Box 26)
- Roman, Chet, The Gay Ghouls, Greenleaf Classics, GL 155, 1970 (Box 26)
- Roman, Chet, His Muscled Lover, Phenix Publishers, PR 245, 1970 (Box 45)
- Roman, Chet, The Gay Gringos, Phenix Publishers, PR 272, 1970 (Box 45)
- Roman, Mark, Hardon Beach, Star Dist., SPADE 106, 1972 (Box 65)
- Rome, Jerry, The Straight Go-Go Boy, Gay Parisian Press, GPP 105, 1970 (Box 19)
- Rose, Dustin, Fiery Fists, Surree Ltd, HIS 69207, 1977 (Box 75)
- Rose, Dustin, Fist Of Fire, Surrey House, MH 446, 1974 (Box 82)
- Rose, Dustin, Golden Showers, Surrey House, HIS6939, 1972 (Box 92)
- Ross, Jerry, Boy Lovers, Continental Classics, CC-290, 1969 (Box 14)
- Ross, Johnny, Golden Shower Chicken, Greenleaf Classics, AC 325, 1984 (Box 23)
- Ross, Johnny, Chicken Stuff, Greenleaf Classics, AC 330, 1984 (Box 23)
- Ross, Johnny, Son On A Leash, Greenleaf Classics, AC 348, 1985 (Box 23)
- Rossi, George, The Star's Lovers, Numbers, 10001, 1978 (Box 37)
- Rossi, George, The Star's Boy Lovers, Star Dist., WB 117, 1975 (Box 68)
- Rowen, Brad, Two Hunk Lovers, Arena, PF-150, 1985 (Box 3)
- Rowen, Stuart, Hung Straight, Surree Ltd, HIS 69158, 1976 (Box 73)
- Rowen, Stuart, First-Time Chicken, Surree Ltd, HIS 69175, 1976 (Box 74)
- Rowen, Stuart, First Time Chicken, Surree Ltd, HIS 69268, 1978 (Box 78)
- Rowen, Stuart, Boarding House Chicken, Surree Ltd, MH 490, 1978 (Box 83)
- Rowen, Stuart, Choice Chicken, Surree Ltd, SS 006, 1975 (Box 84)
- Rowen, Stuart, Butch Bi-Trucker, Surree Ltd, SS 028, 1976 (Box 85)
- Rowen, Stuart, Teen Trainer, Surree Ltd, SS 032, 1976 (Box 85)
- Rowen, Stuart, Big Boss Buck, Surree Ltd, SS 043, 1978 (Box 85)
- Rowen, Stuart, Lay 'Em Straight, Surree Ltd, SSS 106, 1981 (Box 86)
- Rowen, Stuart, Break-In Boy, Surrey House, HIS 69182, 1976 (Box 74)
- Royce, Roger, Gay Gang-Up, P. E. C., FL 90, 1970 (Box 52)
- Rulen, Brad, Teenage Rider, Rough Trade, RT 426, n.d. (Box 54)
- Russell, Thomas, The Edge Of Sin, GX, Inc., SP 116, 1973 (Box 29)
- Russell, Thomas, Loving Michael, GX, Inc., TC 282, 1974 (Box 32)
- Russell, Thomas, San Francisco Slave Boy, Star Dist., CC-102, n.d. (Box 59)
- Ryan, Shad, Ass Hole Buddies, Star Dist., SPADE 107, 1972 (Box 65)
- Ryan, Tom, The Preacher's Boys, Star Dist., WB 113, 1975 (Box 67)
- Ryder, O. B., Mouth For Dick, Surrey House, HIS 69131, 1975 (Box 72)
- Sage, Buck, Western Mouthful, Surree Ltd, HIS 69208, 1977 (Box 75)
- Sage, Buck, The Telephone Installer, Surree Ltd, MH 482, 1978 (Box 83)
- Sage, Buck, Road Gang, Surree Ltd, SSS 104, 1980 (Box 86)
- Saison, Jacques, Man To Man, Brandon House, 3040, 1968 (Box 12)
- Saison, Jacques, The Man's Man, Lambda Press, LB 105, 1968 (Box 33)
- Salter, Harold, Humping Hitchhiker, Star Dist., Club 122, 1973 (Box 59)
- Sampson, David, Hunky Jock, Arena, PF-106, 1983 (Box 3)
- Samson, Roger, Dynamite Dick, Surree Ltd, HIS 69239, 1978 (Box 77)
- Samson, Roger, Dick Enough, Surrey House, HIS 06948, 1973 (Box 70)
- Sand, Carter, Two For The Money, GX, Inc., TC 275, 1973 (Box 32)
- Sanderson, Douglas, Dark Passions Subdue, Avon Publications, AT-67, 1952 (Box 92)
- Sanderson, Loren, Eden Reconsidered, Blueboy Library, 80040, 1977 (Box 8)
- Sanderson, Loren, A Rich Man's Closet, Blueboy Library, 80055, 1977 (Box 9)
- Sanderson, Loren, Queen Of Club, Blueboy Library, 80077, 1977 (Box 10)
- Sanderson, Loren, Tonguing Tony's, Surrey House, MH 452, 1974 (Box 82)
- Santorini, John, Cops & Throbbers, Surrey House, MH 477, 1975 (Box 83)
- Sarrow, Russ, The Gay Game, Exotik Book, W-10, 1965 (Box 17)
- Saunders, Robert, The Gay Lords, Unique, -0-, 1966 (Box 88)
- Savage, Lon, "Big Red", Blueboy Library, 80069, 1977 (Box 9)
- Savage, Lon, Knave Of Diamonds, Blueboy Library, 80073, 1977 (Box 9)
- Savage, Lon, Ace Of Spades, Blueboy Library, 80083, 1977 (Box 10)
- Savage, Lon, Hunky Trade, Surree Ltd, HIS 69236, 1978 (Box 76)
- Savage, Lynn, Travelin' Trick, Surrey House, HIS 69105, 1974 (Box 72)
- Savage, Lynn, Horse Hung, Surrey House, HIS 69112, 1974 (Box 72)
- Savoy, Sam, Hot And Hard, Surrey House, MH 461, 1974 (Box 82)
- Sawyer, Leo, Blind Windows, Blueboy Library, BB 113, 1978 (Box 11)
- Sawyers, Rod, The Flesh Mast, Brandon House, 3073, 1969 (Box 13)
- Sawyers, Rod, Jock, Greenleaf Classics, GL 108, 1969 (Box 25)
- Sawyers, Rod, Fly Boys, Greenleaf Classics, PR 320, 1971 (Box 47)
- Sawyers, Rod, Sunday's Child, GX, Inc., TC 263, 1973 (Box 31)
- Sawyers, Rod, Gay Blades, Parisian Press, P 204, 1971 (Box 41)
- Sawyers, Rod, The Birds And The Boys, Phenix Publishers, PR 236, 1969 (Box 44)
- Saxon, Grant Tracy, The Happy Hustler, Warner Books, 0-446-59691-4, 1975 (Box 88)
- Saxon, Vin, Whisper of Silk, P.E.C., FL5, 1966 (Box 92)
- Scander, Rudy, The Star's Young Boyfriend, Star Dist., Club 119, 1973 (Box 59)
- Schaeffer, Parker, Hank's Navy Buddies, Star Dist., SPADE 131, 1973 (Box 66)
- Scharde, Bernard, Happy Makes It Big, Greenleaf Classics, PR 304, 1971 (Box 46)
- Scharde, Bernard, Happy-Go-Lightly, Phenix Publishers, PR 279, 1970 (Box 46)
- Scharde, Bernard, Pretty Boy, Phenix Publishers, PR 284, 1970 (Box 46)
- Schooter, J. W., Snow Blower, Star Dist., AGR 171, 1987 (Box 68)
- Schooter, J. W., Teenie Wienies, Star Dist., AGR 168, 1987 (Box 68)
- Schrader, Bert, The Tender Trapper, Phenix Publishers, PR 285, 1970 (Box 46)
- Schreiber, Maynard, Rugged Top Man, Star Dist., SS-1010, 1976 (Box 66)
- Scott, D. A., Freshman Initiation, Surey Books, HIS 69472, 1984 (Box 80)
- Scott, Howard, Big, Black Dick, Star Dist., BD 1004, n.d. (Box 58)
- Scott, Mark, Hard Riders, Surree Ltd, SSS 110, 1981 (Box 86)
- Scott, Michael, Quarter Million Piece, Blueboy Library, BB 114, 1978 (Box 11)
- Scott, Michael, Greek Lover, Blueboy Library, BB 126, 1978 (Box 11)
- Scott, Michael, The Killer Queens, Corinth Pubns., CB 550, 1968 (Box 43)
- Scott, Michael, Gay Exorcist, Midwood, 508-60647, 1976 (Box 35)
- Scott, Michael, Gay Cruise, Midwood, 508-60663, 1976 (Box 35)
- Scott, Michael, Private Passions, Midwood, 508-60696, 1976 (Box 35)
- Scott, Michael, Gay Psycho, Midwood, 508-60715, 1976 (Box 35)
- Scott, Michael, Trucker's Chicken, Surey Books, AGR 111, 1983 (Box 68)
- Scott, Michael, Macho Studs, Surey Books, HIS 69491, 1985 (Box 80)
- Scott, Michael, Mouth Piece, Surey Books, SSS 116, 1981 (Box 86)
- Scott, Michael, Small-Town Stud, Surey Books, SSS 127, 1982 (Box 87)
- Scott, Michael, Dark Desires, Surey Books, HIS 69474, 1984 (Box 80)
- Scott, Michael, Skin-Flick Studs, Surree House, HIS 69213, 1977 (Box 76)
- Scott, Michael, Big Stinger, Surree Ltd, HIS 69194, 1977 (Box 75)
- Scott, Michael, College Jocks, Surree Ltd, HIS 69198, 1977 (Box 75)
- Scott, Michael, Full Throat, Surree Ltd, HIS 69201, 1977 (Box 75)
- Scott, Michael, English Leather, Surree Ltd, HIS 69210, 1977 (Box 75)
- Scott, Michael, Hard Hat Master, Surree Ltd, HIS 69222, 1977 (Box 76)
- Scott, Michael, Chicken In Trouble, Surree Ltd, HIS 69266, 1978 (Box 78)
- Scott, Michael, Biker In Bondage I, Surree Ltd, HIS 69277, 1979 (Box 78)
- Scott, Michael, Biker In Bondage Ii, Surree Ltd, HIS 69281, 1979 (Box 78)
- Scott, Michael, Leather Bound, Surree Ltd, MH 481, 1978 (Box 83)
- Scott, Michael, Trickin' With Dad, Surey Books, HIS 69445, 1982 (Box 80)
- Scott, Michael, S & M Bike Slave, Surrey House, HIS 69179, 1976 (Box 74)
- Scott, Michael, Training Buddies, Surrey House, HIS 69190, 1977 (Box 75)
- Scott, Michael, Threeway Team, Surrey House, HIS 69192, 1977 (Box 75)
- Scott, Michael, Body Guard, Star Distributors, AGR157, 1987 (Box 95)
- Scott, Tony, Gay Island, Publisher's Consultants, BAB 109, 1978 (Box 49)
- Sean, Barnyard Sex, Omega International, -0-, 1978 (Box 40)
- Sean, Cellblock Sex, Omega International, -0-, 1978 (Box 40)
- Sean, Roadside Sex, Omega International, -0-, 1978 (Box 40)
- Sean, Surfside Sex, Omega International, -0-, 1978 (Box 40)
- Sean, Syndicate Sex, Omega International, -0-, 1978 (Box 40)
- Sean, Hardhat Sex, Omega International, -0-, 1978 (Box 40)
- Selegna, Sol, Isle Of Passion, Carlyle Communications, LL0878, n.d. (Box 13)
- Shaft, Roger, Hustler Bar, Publisher's Consultants, GY 105, 1978 (Box 50)
- Shalam, Joseph, Body Embezzlers, Numbers, NIL 100, 1978 (Box 37)
- Shane, Mark, The Lady Was A Man, Fabian Books, Z-103, 1959 (Box 17)
- Sharkey, Barry, Trucker's Boy, Star Dist., HS 123, n.d. (Box 62)
- Sharp, Robert, The Chicken Sailor, Star Dist., SPADE 124, 1973 (Box 65)
- Sharpe, Jack, School Boy Suckers, Star Dist., WB 116, 1975 (Box 68)
- Shearer, Johnny, The Male Hustler, K.D.S., CB 012, 1966 (Box 33)
- Shelby, Byron, The Stud Seeker, Greenleaf Classics, AC 109, 1975 (Box 20)
- Shelby, Mark, I Am A Hollywood Call Boy, Brandon House, 937, 1965 (Box 13)
- Sheldon, J. L., Dominated Boys, Greenleaf Classics, AC 307, 1983 (Box 23)
- Short, Roger, Stud On The Rocks, Guild Press Ltd., RC 124, 1971 (Box 28)
- Shrader, Bert, To Want A Boy, P. E. C., FL 25, 1967 (Box 51)
- Shrader, Bert, House Of Male Order, P. E. C., FL 35, 1968 (Box 51)
- Shrader, Bert, Fee Males, P. E. C., FL 37, 1968 (Box 51)
- Shrader, Bert, Gay Tutor, P. E. C., FL 42, 1968 (Box 51)
- Shrader, Bert, Gay Tutor, P. E. C., FL 73, 1970 (Box 52)
- Shrader, Bert, Fee Males, P. E. C., FL 79, 1970 (Box 52)
- Shrader, Bert, To Want A Boy, P. E. C., FL 81, 1970 (Box 52)
- Shrader, Bert, Gay Stud's Trip, P. E. C., FL 32, 1968 (Box 51)
- Shrader, Bert, A Young Man's Fanny, Surrey House, HIS 06973, 1973 (Box 71)
- Shrader, Bert, Hot Rodding, Surrey House, HIS 06983, 1974 (Box 71)
- Shrader, Bert, Cycle Suck, Surrey House, MH 433, 1974 (Box 81)
- Shulanski, Tex, Saddle Buddy, Hamilton House, RAM 10-103, 1974 (Box 32)
- Shun, Erik, Chicken Farm, Spartacus Books, SB-103, 1975 (Box 16)
- Simon, Mark, Hard In The City, Star Dist., SS-1001, 1976 (Box 66)
- Sims, Sammy Boy, He Loved Dick, Surrey House, MH 443, 1974 (Box 82)
- Sinclair, Bernard, Slave To Leather, Surree Ltd, HIS 69228, 1978 (Box 76)
- Singer, Norman, Up Your Pleasure, Gay Parisian Press, GPP 102, 1970 (Box 19)
- Sinnot, Peter, Young Danny, Unique, -0-, 1966 (Box 88)
- Slade, Rick, Stud Sucker, Star Dist., Club 105, 1973 (Box 59)
- Sloan, Harold, Mountain Man, Surree Ltd, HIS 69425, 1981 (Box 79)
- Smith, Art, Share The Rod, Surrey House, HIS 06952, 1973 (Box 70)
- Smith, Art, Two Holer, Surrey House, MH 410, 1973 (Box 81)
- Smith, Art, Mr. Suck, Surrey House, MH 417, 1973 (Box 81)
- Smith, Art, All Day Sucker, Surrey House, MH 423, 1973 (Box 81)
- Smith, Art, Bunkhouse Boy, Surrey House, MH 434, 1974 (Box 82)
- Smith, Donald, My Gay Diary, Bark Book, -0-, 1969 (Box 6)
- Smith, Dr. Robert, Gay Mystique: How Men Love Men, Proctor File Illus., PF-1006, n.d. (Box 49)
- Smith, Houston, 3 Way-The Only Way, GX, Inc., TC 217, n.d. (Box 30)
- Smith, Houston, 3 Way-The Only Way, Publisher's Consultants, GY 101, 1977 (Box 50)
- Smith, Houston, 3 Way-The Only Way, Publisher's Consultants, LR 104, 1977 (Box 50)
- Smith, Houston, Cell-Mating, Surrey House, HIS 06938, 1972 (Box 70)
- Smith, Jack, The Wild Young Fags, Cameo Library, 8005, 1969 (Box 13)
- Smith, Rick, Back Door Buddies, Star Dist., SPADE 123, 1973 (Box 65)
- Smith, Robin G., My Sex Island, Surree Ltd, HIS 69229, 1978 (Box 76)
- Smith, Rodney, My Lover's Little Brother, Star Dist., Club 109, 1973 (Box 59)
- Smith, Rodney, New York Meat Rack, Star Dist., Club 115, 1973 (Box 59)
- Smith, Stan, Boy Ass For The Trucker, Star Dist., BD 1012, 1976 (Box 59)
- Snyder, Anne, Counter Play, Signet Books, J 9982, 1981 (Box 58)
- Snyder, William, Tory's, Avon, 0-380-76547, 1981 (Box 4)
- Southern, Terry, Candy, Putnam, 1042, 1958 (Box 53)
- Spatari, William Charles, The Magnificent Maricon, Brandon House, 3052, 1969 (Box 12)
- Spatari, William Charles, Five Go Down, Brandon House, 3072, 1969 (Box 12)
- Spatari, William Charles, Weekend Homo, Brandon House, 3036, 1968 (Box 12)
- Spear, Charles, Hot White Suckers, Rough Trade, RT 438, n.d. (Box 55)
- Speare, Charles, Hot Hard Comers, Rough Trade, RT 443, n.d. (Box 55)
- Spinner, Chuck, Sergeant's Boys, Rough Trade, RT 430, 1975 (Box 55)
- Squire, Eugene, Cross-Country Trick, Oracle Books, 88-606, 1969 (Box 40)
- St. Clair, Roger, Caged, Midwood, 508-60798, 1976 (Box 35)
- St. John, Larry, Bang The Boy, Surree Ltd, HIS 69155, 1975 (Box 73)
- St. John, Larry, Prison Pluggers, Surree Ltd, HIS 69163, 1976 (Box 74)
- St. John, Larry, Hard Plowin', Surree Ltd, HIS 69173, 1976 (Box 74)
- St. Lorenz, Jimmy, Prison Isle, Greenleaf Classics, PR 332, 1971 (Box 47)
- Stacey, Stephen, Marooned Male, P. E. C., FL 92, 1970 (Box 52)
- Stare, Frank, Coachsuckers, Surey Books, HIS 69482*, 1984 (Box 80)
- Stark, Ben, Size Queen, Pendulum Books, 0-421, 1970 (Box 43)
- Starr, Elihu, The Rearing Of Lazarus, Surey Books, AGR 103, 1983 (Box 68)
- Starr, Elihu, Forced Entry, Surey Books, HIS 69457, 1983 (Box 80)
- Starr, Michael, Hollywood Homo, P. E. C., FL 15, 1967 (Box 50)
- Starr, Michael, Hollywood Homo, P. E. C., FL 64, 1969 (Box 52)
- Starr, Michael, 1 + 1 = One, PAD Library, EB 510, 1967 (Box 40)
- Stavros, Nick, Boys In The Bed, Midwood, 508-60607, 1970 (Box 35)
- Stearn, Jess, The Sixth Man, MacFadden, MB 60-106, 1961 (Box 35)
- Steele, Harry, Boy Masters, Rough Trade, RT 431, 1975 (Box 55)
- Steele, Nick, Dormitory Tricks, Surree Ltd, HIS 69418, 1980 (Box 79)
- Stein, Jock, The Gay Love Letters, Cameo Library, 928042, 1970 (Box 13)
- Stephens, Mick, Danny Malone's Way, Encounter Books, EE 107, 1978 (Box 16)
- Stephens, Mick, Shooting Schedule, Encounter Books, SB 113, 1978 (Box 16)
- Stevens, Eric, Military Orgy, Parisian Press, P 233, 1972 (Box 42)
- Stevens, Mick, Sado Murder, Surree Ltd, HIS 69252, 1978 (Box 77)
- Stevens, Mick, Teen Slave Ring, Surree Ltd, HIS 69403, 1979 (Box 78)
- Stevens, Warren, The Hustlers, Greenleaf Classics, AC 252, 1981 (Box 22)
- Stevens, Warren, Weekend Cruising, Greenleaf Classics, AC 259, 1981 (Box 23)
- Stevenson, Paul, The Dick Director, Star Dist., Club 120, 1973 (Box 59)
- Stevenson, Paul, The Schoolmaster's Lust, Star Dist., Club 127, 1973 (Box 60)
- Stevenson, Paul, Pretty Boy Lifeguard, Star Dist., SPADE 127, 1973 (Box 65)
- Stevenson, Paul, Norman's Twelve Houseboys, Star Dist., SPADE 132, 1973 (Box 66)
- Stewart, Lon, Back Door Buddy, Surrey House, HIS 69100, 1974 (Box 72)
- Stone, Eric, Dave, unknown, M-110, n.d. (Box 89)
- Stone, Jack, Sailor Jim, Blueboy Library, 80008, 1976 (Box 7)
- Stone, Jack, The Running Man, Blueboy Library, 80022, 1976 (Box 7)
- Stone, Jack, The Coke Runners, Blueboy Library, 80044, 1977 (Box 8)
- Stone, Jack, The Mystery Of Toomey's Island, Blueboy Library, 80065, 1977 (Box 9)
- Stone, Jack, The Running Man, Blueboy Library, CA 105, 1976 (Box 10)
- Stone, Jack, Incestuous Lust, Blueboy Library, BB 106, 1978 (Box 11)
- Stone, Jack, Leather Closet, Blueboy Library, BB 123, 1978 (Box 11)
- Stone, Jack, Bang The Bikers, Blueboy Library, BB 125, 1978 (Box 11)
- Stone, Jack, Semi Rough, Numbers, 10012, 1978 (Box 37)
- Stone, Jack, Hot Bodies, Surree Ltd, SS 033, 1978 (Box 85)
- Stone, Mitch, Kelly's Naked Danger, Arena, PF-135, 1985 (Box 3)
- Stone, Paul, New Boy On The Force, Arena, GAY-122, 1984 (Box 2)
- Stoner, Larry, The Hole Thing, Surrey House, HIS 69129, 1975 (Box 72)
- Storey, David, Radcliffe, Avon, 380-00277-125, 1963 (Box 4)
- Stout, Louis, Long Time Coming, Surrey House, HIS 06957, 1973 (Box 70)
- Strada, Vito Della, Locker-Room Lovers, Midwood Books, 60569, 1971 (Box 92)
- Stroth, Dick, Hunky Lifeguards, Surey Books, SSS 115, 1981 (Box 86)
- Stroth, Dick, Wild Bar, Surree House, HIS 69212, 1977 (Box 76)
- Stroth, Dick, Bondage Boys, Surree Ltd, HIS 69218, 1977 (Box 76)
- Stroth, Dick, Young Hunk, Surree Ltd, HIS 69226, 1978 (Box 76)
- Stroth, Dick, Studs For Sale, Surree Ltd, HIS 69238, 1978 (Box 77)
- Stroth, Dick, Growing Up Hard, Surree Ltd, HIS 69415, 1980 (Box 79)
- Stroth, Dick, Toppin' Jocks, Surree Ltd, SS 056, 1979 (Box 86)
- Strotherman, Richard, Trucker's Load, Surree Ltd, HIS 69243, 1978 (Box 77)
- Strotherman, Richard E., Roman Slave Boys, Blueboy Library, 80064, 1977 (Box 9)
- Strotherman, Richard J., Basket Case, Surree Ltd, SS 037, 1978 (Box 85)
- Stryker, Jack, The Layout, GX, Inc., TC 221, n.d. (Box 30)
- Stryker, Jack, The Swab's Out, GX, Inc., TC 227, n.d. (Box 30)
- Stryker, Jack, Ride A Cocked Thumb, GX, Inc., TC 232, n.d. (Box 30)
- Stryker, Jack, The (Almost) Lone Ranger, GX, Inc., TC 248, 1973 (Box 31)
- Stryker, Jack, Death Wish, GX, Inc., TC 265, 1973 (Box 32)
- Stuart, Chad, Flight Into Sodomy, Arena, GB 103, 1978 (Box 2)
- Stuart, Chad, Montana Bound, Arena, GB 105, 1978 (Box 2)
- Stuart, Chad, Men In Heat, Arena, GB 111, 1978 (Box 2)
- Stuart, Chad, Up On The Floor, Arena, GB 119, 1978 (Box 2)
- Stuart, Chad, K-Ymca, Arena, GB 124, 1979 (Box 2)
- Stuart, Chad, The Siegfried Mating, Blueboy Library, 80089, 1977 (Box 10)
- Stuart, Chad, Beat The Man Down, Greenleaf Classics, AC 106, 1975 (Box 20)
- Stuart, Chad, Shaft Man, Greenleaf Classics, GN 406, 1973 (Box 24)